let's talk about Alba Carrillo if I
vamos a comentar lo de Alba Carrillo si
find it and let's talk about something
lo encuentro y vamos a comentar una cosa
about Carlota corredera Look,
de Carlota corredera Mirad
on one hand there would be this clip okay I'll
por un lado estaría este clip vale que
put it very quickly it's Alba Carrillo
lo pongo muy rapidito es Alba Carrillo
The other day at the Barbie premiere
El otro día en la premiere de Barbie
let him slander quietly but without a
déjalo que difame tranquilo pero sin
promo please Look This was the other
promo por favor Mira Esto fue el otro
day at the Barbie premiere I'm
día de la premiere de Barbie estoy
seeing that Cristinini is very trendy
viendo que cristinini es muy tendencia
The Grand Prix has already started The
ya ya ha empezado El Gran Prix
Grand Prix has already started
ha empezado ya el Grand Prix
Look the Grand Prix has started
Mira ha empezado el gran pri
Well then I'll take a look to see
Bueno luego le echaré un vistazo a ver
how it went
qué tal ha ido
listen to me
escúchame
if you want to see my opinion of Barbie you
si queréis ver mi opinión de Barbie la
have it on Javi the little one okay Look
tenéis en el Javi el canijo vale Mirad
This is what Alba Carrillo said the other day
Esto fue lo que dijo el otro día Alba
about us pouring borne at the
Carrillo sobre vertimos borne en la
Barbie premiere okay
premiere de Barbie vale
I can't stand Bertín I was
yo a Bertín no le soporto estaba
Wishing that or rather she Bertín can't stand it that she
Deseando que o sea que ella Bertín no lo
was wishing
soporta que estaba deseando
No Wishing for this to happen to her but yes she
No Deseando que le pasara esto pero sí
is a person who hasn't been able to
que es una persona que no se ha podido
talk has done something It's that when she
hablar ha hecho algo Es que cuando ya
was already in Survivors she did in your house
estaba en supervivientes hizo en tu casa
or in mine with Feliciano what
o en la mía con Feliciano que vaya
destroglodytes okay  she hates it she hates it a
destrogloditas vale lo odia lo odia un
piece of [ __ ] yes a total piece of [ __ ] a [ __ ] pain in the ass
truño sí un truño total un [__] [__]
Well there are some nice things eh There are some things that are nice What
Bueno hay cosas guapas eh Hay cosas que
happens is that they
están guapas Lo que pasa que la han
screwed up But well yesterday yesterday I talked at
cagado Pero bueno ayer ayer hablé largo
length about that movie on Javier
y tendido de esa película en el Javier
canijo in case you want to know okay But
canijo por si queréis saber vale Pero
well the question here is Alba Carrillo
bueno la cuestión aquí es Alba Carrillo
Alba Javi saw the new setas del jujos
Alba Javi viste el nuevo setas del jujos
Jujuy looks really cool on him who is the
le quedó muy chulo el Jujuy que es el
Juan hus
Juan hus
No I haven't seen it I haven't seen it honey
No no lo he visto no lo he visto corazón
but well I'm happy about everything that
pero bueno yo me alegro de todo lo que
happens to him Well everyone let's see here
le pase Bueno a todo el mundo a ver aquí
Alba Carrillo what she's saying is
Alba Carrillo lo que está diciendo es
that she really wants to get over Bertín
que que le tiene muchas ganas a Bertín
Osborne that she's really mad at Bertín
osborne que le tiene mucha rabia Bertín
Osborne for a in your house and in mine
osborne por un en tu casa y en la mía
another one I always always say in your house is
otra siempre siempre digo en tu casa es
mine she sees it like I'm hornier than
la mía lo ve como estoy más caliente que
being a bingo in your house in your house is
el ser un bingo en tu casa en tu casa es
mine was a program that I watched with
la mía era un programa que yo veía con
my wife when we were boyfriend and girlfriend in the
mi mujer cuando éramos novios en el
car the two of us lying there because
coche los dos allí tirados porque
we have well anyway no it's that it's
tenemos bueno en fin no que es que se me
going away I'm  it's getting out of hand
está yendo se me está yendo de las manos
in your house and in mine in your house and in
en tu casa y en la mía en tu casa y en
mine it was a program that was on
la mía era un programa que echaban en
los 40 presented by Daniela bloome
los 40 que lo presentaba Daniela bloome
and Uri Sabbath Okay and it was a
y Uri Sabbath Vale y era un programa
sex program and I watched it with my wife when
sexual y lo veía yo con mi mujer cuando
we were both boyfriend and girlfriend and it's really good
éramos los dos novios y está muy bien
okay And it
vale Y
caught on and whenever I'm going to mention
cogió y siempre que me voy a mencionar
Bertín's program I always say in your
el programa de Bertín siempre digo en tu
house it's mine and it's not called in your house
casa es la mía y no se llama en tu casa
in mine it's called something similar,
en la mía se llama algo parecido lo de
Bertín's but I always say in your house in
Bertín pero siempre digo en tu casa en
mine well Well it turns out that at one
la mía bueno Pues resulta ser que en un
point Bertín while they
momento dado Bertín mientras que esto
were surviving invited Félix to
estaban supervivientes invitó a Félix a
Feliciano and Alba Carrillo has been
Feliciano y Alba Carrillo se la tiene
swearing ever since what's going on
jura desde entonces qué es lo que pasa
because I've been watching the
porque yo me he estado viendo la
interview that Bertín did with
entrevista que le hizo Bertín a
Feliciano and I've seen the whole part where they
Feliciano y he visto toda la parte en la
talk about Alba Carrillo
que hablan de Alba Carrillo
and they don't say anything bad and they don't say anything
y no dicen nada malo y no dicen nada
bad come on the cabin in the cave and
malo venga la cabaña en la cueva y
then I have him sentenced apart from
entonces yo le tengo sentenciado aparte
his children go to mine's school and as a
sus hijos van al Cole del mío y como
father well I never saw him I've never
padre pues este jamás le vi Nunca le he
seen him look what  He says here, eh, look what he
visto mira lo que dice aquí eh mira lo
says here, I never saw him, she is here, I
que dice aquí jamás le vi ella está o
mean, he has his kids in the same school
sea él tiene los niños en el mismo Cole
as mine and I never saw him because he never,
que los míos y jamás le vi porque nunca
never, I mean, here he's saying like
nunca o sea aquí está diciendo como que
he never shows up, the thing about the
él nunca se presenta la cosa de a las
kids' things, that he's not seen
cosas de los hijos que no se le ve por
there because of school, you know, I've
allí por por el colegio me entiende
never seen him, I've never seen him, I've never
Nunca le he visto no le he visto nunca
seen him, stay with this phrase,
le he visto quedaros con esta frase
whatever the reason, it portrays
sea por el motivo que sea retrata muy
Bertin very well, I don't think
bien a Bertín yo no creo que en esta
Alba Carrillo is right on this one, a
tenga la razón Alba Carrillo
meeting I saw him once at a
una reunión Le he visto una vez en una
Christmas party but what
fiesta de navidad pero lo que dicen
all the parents say is that they weren't
todos los padres es que no se les
first told I never saw him, I never saw him
primero ha dicho Nunca le vi nunca le vi
Well, I saw him once at a
Bueno lo he visto una vez en una fiesta
Christmas party but what everyone says is, have you
de navidad pero lo que dicen todos los
seen him, you've never seen him, he came to me, have you
has visto no lo has visto nunca le vino
seen her or haven't you seen him And he says
la has visto o no lo has visto Y dice
Well, I saw him once at a
Bueno lo he visto una vez en una fiesta
Christmas party okay And now he says Well, what
de Navidad vale Y ahora dice Bueno lo
all the parents say is but so, I
que dicen todos los padres es pero así
mean, no, you don't trust when he
que o sea que no no confías en cuando él
says, I'm going to pretend, listen to me,
dice yo me voy a hacer a ver escúchame
one thing is that being parents is much more than
una cosa es que ser padres mucho más que
paying It's that if not How many parents  there wouldn't
pagar Es que si no Cuántos padres no
be it's that father is the upbringing of course
habría es que padre es la crianza claro
Here he is mentioning more or less that
Aquí está mencionando más o menos que
Bertín maybe doesn't act as much of a
Bertín a lo mejor no ejerce mucho de
father because they don't show up at
padre porque no se presentan las
meetings, at parties and all that, okay.
reuniones a las fiestas y demás vale
But now look at what it says here,
Pero ahora fíjate lo que dice aquí
you know that he's really mad at Bertín, they're
sabes que le tiene mucha rabia a Bertín
really mad at Bertín because of
le tienen mucha rabia a Bertín por una
an interview at your house at mine
por una entrevista en tu casa en la mía
that I was watching the other day
que yo la estuve viendo el otro día
because to find out what they
porque para informarme a ver qué es lo
were talking about, I
que estaban hablando me tragué la me
swallowed the interview with Feliciano and he doesn't
tragué la entrevista de Feliciano y no
say anything, he doesn't say anything more, he doesn't say
dice nada no dice nada más chicha no
anything at all, he doesn't even say
dice nada de nada No dice ni siquiera
anything against her, I mean, the only thing I did
nada contra ella o sea lo único que hice
against her is that, well, what a
contra ella es que bueno que hay que ver
shame, what a shame,
qué pena que hay que ver qué pena
after so many years and so many
después de tantos años y tantas
dreams, well, since things are over, that
ilusiones pues como ha terminado la cosa
's the only thing he says, boy, and then they
es lo único que dice muchacho y luego se
start talking in that interview about all the
ponen a hablar en esa entrevista de la
things that Alba has said about him, she
de cosas que ha dicho Alba de él que ha
even went so far as to insinuate that he didn't
llegado a insinuar incluso que a él no
like women, well, that's all there is
le gustaban las mujeres vamos y es que
here, look,
eso está aquí mira
luckily I have a newspaper archive here,
por suerte tengo yo aquí una hemeroteca
look,
mira
look at Alba Carrillo's covers about
Mira las portadas de Alba Carrillo sobre
Feliciano  Look, look,
Feliciano mira mira
Feliciano asked me for a divorce in a
Feliciano me ha pedido el divorcio de
cold and distant way. She wanted me to
manera fría y distante ella quería que
ask him for a divorce in a
le pidiera el divorcio de manera
hot way. Okay. And this headline is okay. This
calentita vale Y este titular vale Esto
is what Feliciano is saying in the
es lo que Comenta Feliciano en la
interview. We converted Borne. Felix wasn't that into
entrevista convertimos borne a Félix no
women. Of
le ponía mucho las mujeres
course, the guy says that when she
claro el muchacho dice que cuando ella
did this cover, he started
hizo esta portada que a él le empezaron
getting proposals that aren't
a llegar propuestas que no tienen nada
bad at all. I've said this many times. I
de malo yo lo he dicho muchas veces
wish I had been bisexual so I'd
Ojalá yo hubiera sido bisexual así
have more to choose from, but I don't
tendría más donde elegir pero no me
like men. Of course, he started
gustan los hombres claro empezaron a
getting proposals for male flirtations.
llegarle propuestas de ligoteos
Once he told me that we could also
alguna vez me dijo que igual podíamos
call someone else. I mean, he wanted
Llamar a otra persona O sea que quería
that threesome.
ese tríos
They came in and out of our house. As he
entraban y salían de nuestra casa A su
pleased.
antojo
Feliciano marries that poor girl
Feliciano se casa con esa Pobre niña
to whitewash his image.
para blanquear su imagen
Anyway, a lot of nonsense. And I've seen
en fin un montón de movidas y he visto
the interview that Bertin and the
la entrevista que le hace Bertín y el
guy are doing. The only thing he's talking about is
muchacho lo único que está hablando Es
[Music]
[Música]
about the things that she talked about in
sobre las cosas que ha hablado ella en
the magazine, but he doesn't say anything, eh, I mean, he doesn't
la revista pero no dice nada eh o sea no
insult her, he doesn't disrespect her, they don't say
la insulta no la falta respeto no dicen
anything, a bargain, they just say, you have to look at it
nada un ganga solo dicen hay que verlo
carefully, the illusion that we had.  I know what it's
bien la ilusión que teníamos no sé qué
worth And let live and that woman who I think
vale Y deja vivir y esa mujer que creo
is a physiotherapist who is surely
que es fisioterapeuta que seguro que es
super autonomous that she is going to have, did
súper Autónoma que va a tener
n't Bertín ask the other day that out of
no pidió Bertín el otro día que por
camaraderie they respect her with her subject and she got
compañerismo le respetaran con su tema y
angry with several for touching on the
se cabreó con varias por tocar el tema
current subject Well, she will have what she
de actualidad Pues algo opinará lo que
wants to say about the interview happy but the thing is
quiera de la entrevista feliz pero es
that you can have what you want to say about
que tú puedes opinar lo que quieras de
an interview but what you cannot have an
una entrevista pero lo que no puedes
opinion is what has not happened
opinar es lo que no ha pasado
or rather is that interview is on
o sea es que esa entrevista está en
Telecinco you can look for it, put it Bertín
telecinco podéis buscarla poner Bertín
Osborne Feliciano put it yes I showed
osborne Feliciano ponerlo si es que la
it the other day in a video I think he
saqué el otro día en un vídeo creo que
put a piece of the interview for the
puso un trozo la entrevista para lo
only thing that Alba is mentioned is what I
único que se menciona Alba es lo que os
'm telling you you have to see what a shame with
estoy contando hay que ver qué pena con
the illusion that we had no And how
la ilusión que teníamos no Y cómo ha
things ended also and the things that
terminado la cosa además y las cosas que
such well the things that she has been saying
tal bueno las cosas que ha ido diciendo
about me that I want the best for her
de mí que yo quiero lo mejor para ella
that they are survivors and
que están supervivientes y me están
these things that she has said
llegando estas cosas que ha dicho ella
on a cover are reaching me it doesn't say anything true I
en una portada no dice nada de verdad lo
promise your son that he has it that he
prometo tu hijo que lo tenga que se
forgets when before the father that that has
olvide cuando antes del padre que eso sí
been  an accident the father not the
que ha sido un accidente el padre no el
son it's not that big a deal
hijo es que tampoco es para tanto
and
y
[Music]
[Música]
then it came up it came
después
up but it's
ha surgido ha surgido pero es que de
really I mean when this man or
verdad O sea cuando este señor o sea
this thing this thing that is still
esta cosa esta cosa que sí que todavía
circulating in Spain but he keeps quiet
pululando por España pero es que calla
because since we don't dare to go and vote
que como no nos animamos a ir a votar
he and his colleagues are going to be our
ese y sus colegas van a ser los
representatives on earth I mean it
representantes en la tierra o sea es que
scares me so much that my legs are shaking
me da un miedo que me tiemblan las patas
and I haven't had any wine after this
y no me he tomado vino después de este
speech
speech
so it has to be Oh I do
pues hay que ser Ay
n't know which ones
no sé cuáles
please put it on for me
por favor pónmelo
okay it's okay Well we'll do it in
bueno no pasa nada Pues lo hacemos en
two Ah now we are we are we can
dos Ah que ahora sí que estamos que
see okay we are
estamos que se nos ve vale que estamos
in two batches as you are saying
en dos tandas como bien estáis diciendo
the henchmen of pouring
los secuaces de vertir los tentáculos de
Bertín's tentacles are very long Because
Bertín son muy alargados Porque además
he also announces What is the name of cans of
él anuncia Cómo se llama latas de
seafood
marisco
it's an octopus with super super tentacles Well that's
es un pulpo con tentáculos súper súper
it son Bertín I can't stand you
Pues eso hijo Bertín que no te soporto
You are the most rancid there is in Spain
Eres de lo más rancio que hay en España
the most rancid you do not represent us and now
lo más rancio no nos representas y ya
with this last [ __ ] of this Poor
con esta última [__] de esta Pobre
woman I mean she was come on sir
mujer O sea que ella fue vamos señor
come on sir go on And how  he put me
venga señor anda Y como me puso a mí
when I separated it's that I don't but it's that
cuando me separé es que me no pero es
don't tell me to stop it's that how he
que no me digas que me pare es que cómo
put me is that really Or rather he
me puso a mí es que de verdad O sea que
hasn't said anything about her unless
no ha dicho nada de ella a no ser que
that part doesn't throw his life away
esa parte no eche su vida en ninguna
anywhere if you find it please
parte si la encontráis por favor me lo
send it to me man But I want to know the
mandáis hombre Pero quiero saber la
truth if he put her down he put her down you
verdad si él la puso verde la puso verde
have to
hay
put it to me one day that I'm going to answer them
que me lo pones un día que les voy a
And if we have to rescue him in your house in
Y si hay que rescatar él en tu casa en
mine
la mía
in your house or in mine it's that she has
en tu casa o en la mía es que ella ha
said the same thing as me
dicho lo mismo que yo
in your house is mine she said Alba has
en tu casa es la mía ha dicho Alba ha
mine about Bertín and put it to me one day
la mía de Bertín y me lo pones un día
that I'm going to tell them we have to rescue one
que les voy a contar hay que rescatar un
day his statements in your house
día las declaraciones de él en tu casa
in mine he has said the same thing as me look
en la mía ha dicho lo mismo que yo mira
in your house
en tu casa
or in mine
o en la mía
in your house or in mine there's
en tu casa o en la mía
nothing on the internet about that it's that it's
no hay nada en internet sobre eso es que
very old
es muy antiguo
there are other movies that are called the same
hay otras películas que se llaman igual
in your house of mine it no longer exists of course
en tu casa de la mía ya no existe claro
my house is yours it's called Bertín's thing
mi casa es la tuya se llama lo de Bertín
Look  how much I disliked Bertín I mean I
Fíjate lo mal que me caía Bertín o sea
empathized with Feliciano I won't tell you anymore
empaticé con Feliciano no te digo más
laughing and you would go it's survivors No
riéndose y tú irías es supervivientes No
because you don't have balls You know why you have to
porque no tenéis huevos Sabes porque hay
raise your children then
que sacar a los hijos adelante entonces
neither of you have balls you
ninguno de los dos tiene huevos tú
have to go to
tienes que ir a
says Alan I'm talking about that she's very
dice Alan hablo de que ella está muy
upset with Bertín for that
molesta con Bertín por aquella
senseless interview look at him He
entrevista sin sentido
really is over there he went up
míralo De verdad está por ahí subió
and the other Well he's already retired Thank you
y el otro Bueno ya está retirado Gracias
but you love ah there's something on
pero te quieres ah que hay algo en
Spanish television from your house in mine you do
televisión española de tu casa en la mía
n't have to
no
have balls to do this
hay que tener huevos para hacer este
type then there's a movie there's a
tipo entonces hay una película hay una
movie
película
[Music]
[Música]
say that he's not going to miss the
decir que no le va a faltar el colegio
private school in your house or in mine on
de pago en tu casa o en la mía en
Spanish television But that in your
televisión española Pero eso que en tu
house or in mine
casa o en la mía
past in mine
pasado en la mía
interview programs on TV it's
programas de entrevista en tv
true it's true
es verdad es verdad
in yours or in mine it's called
en la tuya o en la mía se llama
in yours or in mine it's true it's
en la tuya o en la mía es verdad es
true It's the same program as Bertín
verdad Él es el mismo programa de Bertín
but on Spanish television in yours or
pero en televisión española en la tuya o
in mine look with Iker Casillas with Paco
en la mía mira con Iker casilla con Paco
León it's true look Well that's why it's
León es verdad mira
mess that's why it's the mess of
Pues por eso es el lío por eso es el lío
course that's where the son comes from that's where Leo comes from who
claro de ahí viene el hijo de ahí viene
was also my son's because
que además era el de mi hijo porque a
the other two take them to my son's so that's why
los otros dos Les lleva al de mi hijo
I Bertin really is a
entonces por eso yo Bertín de verdad un
guy who hasn't even greeted me at a school dance.
tío que ni un baile del colegio me ha
Of course there isn't one either
saludado yo Por supuesto tampoco hay
but the wronged one has been me it goes
pero es que la agraviada ha sido yo va
with the age that no one looks at what is
con la edad que ningún mira lo que está
saying here that he
diciendo aquí que ningún baile del
hasn't even greeted me at a school dance but if in the
colegio me ha saludado pero si en el
other click on the Barbie thing he said that he has
otro clic en lo de Barbie ha dicho que
never seen it
no lo ha visto nunca
That's the one
Ese es esa
Yes yes yes I put it the other day I put it the
Sí sí sí lo puse el otro día lo puse el
other day
otro día
in case you want to see it because I
por si lo queréis ver
saw it I saw it Feliciano
que es que la vi Es que la vi Feliciano
Speaks for the first time about his divorce
Habla por primera vez sobre su divorcio
from Alba Carrillo okay For me it was very
de Alba Carrillo vale Para mí fue muy
hard because I had already put a lot of
duro porque ya había puesto mucha
hope if they don't say anything bad they don't
ilusión si es que no dicen nada malo no
say anything bad it's because I saw him damn what does it
dicen nada malo es que lo vi [__]
matter but it's that I don't like him
que tiene que no importa pero es que me
So I'm not going to say
cae mal Entonces ya no voy a decir lo de
the age thing anymore it's that I don't like him eh
la edad es que es que me cae mal eh
Even if he were 20 years old he goes with a with the
Aunque tuviera 20 años va con un con el
black turtleneck sweater that I say
jersey de cuello vuelto negro que digo
real boy who told you that
chico de verdad quién te ha dicho que
calming at all hours now with
sosegante a todas horas ya con
little balls and everything and one and a
pelotillas y de todo y una y una bomba
leather bomb here she's messing with
de cuero aquí se está metiendo con la
clothes that I don't see as necessary brown it
ropa que tampoco lo veo necesario marrón
's that they are personal attacks 2017 tesa
es que son ataques personales 2017 tesa
because it's when she were
porque es cuando ella estaban
survivors like that guys Enough say
supervivientes así chicos Ya basta
hello to other parents socialize because it's that
saluda a otros padres relacionate porque
I talk to everyone that girl
es que yo hablo con todos a esa chica
please that very cute girl that woman
por favor esa chica monísima esa mujer
who is now pregnant with
que está embarazada ahora del futuro
Bertín's future child that I saw her and she seems like
vástago de Bertín que la vi y me parece
a posh woman I think she's a
una pitucada de mujer creo que es
physiotherapist or some kind of girl But
fisioterapeuta o sea una tía tal Pero
how do you get involved with Bertín Of course she'll
cómo te enrollas con Bertín Claro que ya
tell me and you and you What is the history you
me dirá y tú y tú Qué es el historial
have well that's why that's why I tell you
que tienes pues por eso por eso te digo
a girl like you what are you doing with that man
una tía como tú qué haces con ese hombre
please not even with a WiFi stick
por favor ni con un palo WiFi
It's that I see you too tough I see you
Es que la veo demasiado dura la veo
too tough for what you will see that it's not that
demasiado dura para lo que verás tú que
much I don't know I don't see that
tampoco para tanto no sé no veo yo que
Bertín has told her the great thing
Bertín le haya dicho la gran cosa
nor as for this you are
tampoco como para esto
disgusting so much of defending in sight
das asco tanto de defender a la vista
Well yes YouTube Well yes I will be the one who is
Pues sí YouTube Pues sí seré yo el que
disgusting seeing your comment I agree with myself
da asco viendo tu comentario me doy toda
I am the one who gives  disgust for
la razón soy yo el que da asco por
defending sight
defender la vista